

PERSONAL

- Name
 Ansar Shayekin
- Address Kingston Ln, London, Uxbridge UB8 3PH, Bishop Complex UB8 3PH Uxbridge
- Phone number +44 7340416474
- Email 2027628@brunel.ac.uk
- Website
 https://ansar-codes.netlify.app/
- ED LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/ansar shayekin-289880221/

GITHUB

https://github.com/Ansar1337

INTERESTS

- Active Gym Member
- Love reading books
- Traveling
- Coding

ANSAR SHAYEKIN

My name is Ansar Shayekin, I am 19 years old and I am Computer Science Student. I consider myself a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for coding and programming. I am currently in my second year of studying Computer Science: Software Engineering at Brunel University. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am looking for a full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021

IT Specialist (Internship)

QazExpoCongress, Nur-Sultan(Kazakhstan)

- Participated in the creation of distributed, scalable, reliable, and efficient software.
- Determined the possibility of using ready-made software products.
- Participated in the development of new and expansion of existing software products.
- Gained experience in the software development cycles.

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

IT Specialist (Internship)

Karagandaenergoremont JSC, Karaganda(Kazakhstan)

- Prepared the electronic versions of documents and reports of the company.
- Improved my communication skills by helping customers and working as a team member.



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Sep 2020 - Jun 2024

BSc COMPUTER SCIENCE

Brunel University, London

Gained programming knowledge by over 2 years of self-learning and going through two years of University lectures and assignments. Proved a strong holding of problem-solving skills, by finding ways to solve different coding and logical problems, and by making fast decisions, under pressure, in my working

environment.

Sep 2018 - Jun 2020

High School

Spectrum International School, Nur-Sultan(Kazakhstan)

GPA - 3.8

GCSE and AS Levels

Sep 2007 - Jun 2018

Middle School

NurOrda International School, Nur-Sultan(Kazakhstan)

GPA - 3.8



Netflix Copy: This project is a simplified front end clone of Netflix. It was created with React and CSS (Grid and Flexbox). It uses The MovieDB API to search for movies and display details.

- Built it using React, HTML/CSS, Axios, YouTube IFrame Player API and Media queries.
- The full development process is stored on my public GitHub repository for version control.
- Link for the website

Personal portfolio website: Designed and developed a responsive, multi-device and cross-browser compatible personal portfolio website.

- Built it using HTML/CSS and JavaScript.
- The full development process is stored on my public GitHub repository for version control.
- Link for the website

Banking application: Developed a banking application that executes various functions such as: Depositing money, withdrawing money, showing the previous transactions and calculating interest of current funds.

- · Built it using Java.
- The full development process is stored on my public GitHub repository for version control.



SKILLS

Java	****
JavaScript	****
HTML/CSS	****
SQL	****
Git/GitHub	****
React	****



REFERENCES

References available on request.